So the second model customization approaches supervised fine tuning,
used to improve performance on specific tasks such as summarization, Q and A,
to improve style format or depth. Let's say you have built a generative application
that does the summarization, but the response that you are getting from the foundation model
is not good from the style or format perspective. That's where you can use supervised fine tuning.
So training data set of labeled examples used for fine tuning. Remember for supervised
fine tuning you will need labeled examples for fine tuning. So what labeled example means is
you will need to provide the prompt and you will also need to provide the reference response.
And reference response basically means the output you would expect the model to generate for that
particular prompt. Now let's say you built generative A app that does the summarization
for a physician. You sent it a prompt what is type 2 diabetes and the output it generates is
like this dx type 2 dm. So you can see it's in a particular abbreviated clinical style
so you are fine doing it for the style and format. Okay now how does this actually work?
Model learns to a set what type of output should be generated for certain type of inputs.
Now let's take a look at it visually. So here you can see we have this Amazon NOA Pro.
It's the pre-trained base model available in Amazon bedrock. Then the task here is summarization.
So what you're going to do is you're going to have some proprietary label data and we already
discussed labeled it is prompt output pair. So you'll create a training job in the Amazon bedrock
service and behind the scene is going to create a SageMaker training job. So once you uploaded
this proprietary label data in an S3 bucket you created a training job in bedrock. It will create
a SageMaker training job and then fine tune this pre-trained model to a fine tune LLM model.
Then you can send a prompt to this fine tune model and you will get a response.
So here is an example of prompt what is diabetes and in base model maybe you will get something.
Like this but when you have done the fine tuning you will get it in a particular style or format.
So supervised fine tuning is best for structured well defined task with high quality label data.
Okay so that's pretty much it from this lecture. I'll see in the next lecture. Thank you.